<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Dragon's Ores</name>
	<supportedVersions>
	<li>1.0</li>
	<li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
	<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<author>DragonKing</author>
	<packageId>dragonking.dragonsores</packageId>
	<description>
&lt;size=24&gt;"Features"&lt;/size&gt;
This mod adds 11 semi-original fantasy themed metals, that have their own strengths, weaknesses and color. I have attempted to balance them in relation to vanilla ores, as well as comparing them to those found in other mods. The ores are tweaked to be quite rare, but when found, generate in larger quantities. This is done in order to make them useful, but not override to many vanilla (such as steel) and modded (such as iron from materials expanded) spawns for ores that are required in order to build progressing structures and the like.

&lt;size=24&gt;Why did I make this?&lt;/size&gt;
I wanted to make a semi-original fantasy ores mod, that would extend your choices when it comes to metals in buildings and equipment. I wasn't satisfied with other fantasy metal mods on the workshop, as the ones I have tried, tend to make the added materials way to over powered compared to everything else in the game. I also wanted it to not be based on pre-existing, well established ores from pop culture, as it would let it fit into any playthrough better that way. I balanced the stats off of vanilla ores, and compared them to other ore related mods. I didn't want to go too overboard in making these ores overpowered, so the ores have a tradeoff when it comes to their superior stats. I also wanted to add in more vibrant colors, to make these ores stand out more, and provide more color options for things that can only be made out of metal stuffs.

&lt;size=24&gt;What is Included/changed?&lt;/size&gt;
There is a total of 11 ores:
Ambut
Cryolium
Cryppo
Hydrotherium
Loveli
Luxorium
Mythil
Penumbrite
Primoss
Smarat
Vulcanite

Each ore also has a color coded texture in 3 sizes, making it easier to distinguish smaller from larger stacks of ores.

&lt;size=24&gt;What this does not do&lt;/size&gt;
There is no added processes, specific buildings or other game mechanics included that expand the use of the metals beyond what the vanilla game, and other mods might do. Nothing is changed, all the ores are just additive, and inherit the baseline properties in the same way that vanilla ores do. There is also no unique texture for each ore (yet), but I would like to make that eventually if I can. Due to the simplicity of this mod, it is quite stackable with other mods, and could even extend them if they dynamically patch in modded ores.

&lt;size=24&gt;How to use this&lt;/size&gt;
Chuck it into your mod load order wherever you think makes the most sense. If you use other mods that can benefit from modded ores, make sure to place this mod according to those mods guidelines.
	</description>
<modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>Imranfish.XMLExtensions</packageId>
	<displayName>XML Extensions</displayName>
	<downloadUrl>https://github.com/15adhami/XmlExtensions/releases</downloadUrl>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2574315206</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
</modDependencies>
<loadAfter>
    <li>Imranfish.XMLExtensions</li>
</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>